<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Rs0n\'s  Coffee Shop</string>
    <string name="introduction">Rs0n\'s Coffee shop is an Android Application designed with several security vulnerabilities intentionally built in.  Similar to DVWA and the OWASP Juice Shop, this CTF allows penetration testers to expand on their knowledge, improve their techniques, and better prepare real world security assessments.  When a user successfully exploits a vulnerability in this app, she/he will be presented with a toast message containing a unique flag.  Flags may also be present in response objects and or in the form of a hash that can be brute forced.  These flags can then be added to your account at https://rson.com/coffeeshop and a score will be returned depending on the difficulty of the exploit.  My hope is that this tool will help security practitioners, developers, and ethical hackers better understand the vulnerabilities that can exist in modern mobile applications, as well as use this information to help protect real user\'s information. Good Luck!\n\nOh, and there seems to be an issue with the registration at the moment…but I\'m sure you\'ll figure something out. :)</string>
    <string name="githubLink"><a href='https://github.com/R-s0n/SpringBoot-CheatSheet/blob/main/SpringBootNotes.txt\'>Github</a></string>
    <string name="reviewOne">"\&quot;Looks like I'm the first to leave a review on the new app!  I've been coming to Rson\'s coffee for years, they always have amazing service and the coffee is fantastic  I looooove their latte!!  This new app is really cool, but it does seem a bit buggy right now.  I'm sure that'll get worked out soon, though.\&quot;</string>
    <string name="reviewTwo">"\&quot;This messaging feature is really cool!  It's a great way to meet new people in the area.  If anyone wants to meet up for a coffee, send me a message.  My username is OodlesOfPoodles647!!\&quot;</string>
    <string name="reviewThree">"\&quot;Are you kidding me?!?!  I've had better coffee at a gas station!!  This place is soooooo bad!!  And the service SUUUUUUUCKS!  I'll NEVER come back!\&quot;</string>
    <string name="reviewFour">\&quot;What is the point of this app?  I don\'t understand why every small business feels like they have to have this huge online presence.  I just want coffee.  Quit trying to sell me a \'Lifestyle\'…\&quot;</string>
    <string name="reviewFive">\&quot;This place is one of the best coffee shops around!!  I really have to hand it to the manager, Cody Christion, for running such a tight ship.  This place would be LOST without him!!!  In fact, I think the owners should give him a HUGE raise!!!!&quot;</string>
    <string name="reviewSix">\&quot;Nothing to write home about, but this place will do in a pinch.  I\'m very confused, though, as to why they felt the need to make this app.  I guess the order online feature is helpful when it works.&quot;</string>
    <string name="addGiftCardMessage">Good news!!  You can now use your gift cards to pay for orders in our online store!  Simply add the gift card number located at the top right-hand side, along with the three digit security code on the back.</string>
</resources>